{
    "subject": "Jane_Wyman",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Ronald_Reagan",
    "human_readable": "Jane Wyman is married to Ronald Reagan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.988504946231842,
            "question": "Was Ronald Reagan married to Jane Wyman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9881582856178284,
            "question": "Is Ronald Reagan known for being married to Jane Wyman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9176425933837891,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Jane Wyman and Ronald Reagan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8530910611152649,
            "question": "To whom was Jane Wyman married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8465316295623779,
            "question": "Who was Jane Wyman married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8160977959632874,
            "question": "What is the connection between Jane Wyman and Ronald Reagan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8157926201820374,
            "question": "Name a famous person married to Jane Wyman."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.721747100353241,
            "question": "Who was the husband of Jane Wyman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7152704000473022,
            "question": "Who was Jane Wyman's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6220358610153198,
            "question": "With whom did Jane Wyman have a marital relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jane Wyman is married to Ronald Reagan.",
            "html": "yago_28836_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was Jane Wyman's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_28836_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the husband of Jane Wyman?",
            "html": "yago_28836_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a famous person married to Jane Wyman.",
            "html": "yago_28836_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28836_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28836_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28836_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28836_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28836_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28836_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28836_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28836_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28836_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28836_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Jane Wyman is married to Ronald Reagan.\" Specifically, multiple files mention their marriage in 1940 and its dissolution in 1948."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}